threema.ch 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy - Threema

_March 6, 2018_

Threema GmbH (hereafter «Threema») was founded on the premise of bulletproof data protection. It is our primary goal to store only the absolute minimum of information for the shortest possible time («Privacy by Design»). In addition to using state-of-the-art encryption methods, we take all necessary technical and organizational measures to prevent unauthorized data access and misuse. The processing and protection of data is carried out in accordance with applicable legal regulations and EU Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR).

## 1\. General Information

The Threema website can be used completely anonymously and is completely free of advertising, tracking or other analytics software.

## 2\. Purpose of Data Processing

Threema only processes data to respond to your support request or to enable orders in the Threema merchandise shop.

## 3\. Scope and Duration of Data Processing

  * Requests for technical support contain your email address, which is necessary to answer the request. Support requests and all of the associated data will be permanently deleted after 6 months of inactivity. 
  * A session cookie is set to forward the order at our merchandise shop to our sales partner. All session cookies are deleted as soon as the user leaves the Threema website. 

## 4\. Data Processed by Third Parties

The session cookie set by the Threema merchandise shop contains the desired quantity, color and size of an item that is to be ordered and is made available to our sales partner. The cookie does not contain any personal data.

## 5\. Right to Information, Correction, Blocking, Deletion and Objection

You have the right to receive information about your personal data stored by Threema GmbH at any time. Likewise, you have the right to correct, block or (apart from the legally required data storage for business purposes) delete your personal data.

## 6\. Responsible Body

If you have any questions about data protection at Threema GmbH, you can contact us directly. Send us an e-mail to [privacy@threema.ch](mailto:privacy@threema.ch).

Responsible body and direct contact for data protection topics at Threema GmbH:

Threema GmbH  
Data Protection officer  
Churerstrasse 82  
8808 Pfäffikon SZ  
Switzerland  

CHE-221.440.104

Representative in the EU according to Art. 27 para. 1 GDPR: GeKaCe GmbH, Dept. T, Weilerweg 13, 72411 Bodelshausen, Germany

## 7\. Amendment of the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to comply with changed legal requirements or to reflect new functionalities of the app. The current Privacy Policy is always available for consultation from within Threema.

## Disclaimer

This is a mere translation of the German version of this document.

In case of any discrepancies between the English version and the German version of this document, **the German version will prevail**.
